<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on Perfect Dark Mode</title>
    <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on Perfect Dark Mode</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Desktop Setup</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/fedora_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/fedora_setup/</guid>
      <description>When you first download Fedora Workstation, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a little hard to figure out how to make it usable. Especially if you&amp;rsquo;ve never tinkered with Linux before.
Here is how to set up Fedora.
Add badname user $ adduser --badname firstname.lastname $ sudo usermod -aG wheel username
# uncomment this line in the visudo file $ sudo visudo %wheel ALL=(ALL) ALLDelete other user:
$ userdel username
DNF Config (for speed) DNF is one of the package managers that comes with Fedora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources I used to Pass CCNA</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/resources_for_passing_ccna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/resources_for_passing_ccna/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of great CCNA resources out there. This list does not include all of them. Only the ones that I personally used to pass the CCNA 200-301 exam.
Materials for CCNA are generally separated into 5 categories:
Books Video courses Labs Practice test Flashcards Books Wendell Odom OCG Official cert guide library To me, this is the king of CCNA study materials. Some people do not like reading but this will give you more depth than any other resource on this list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RHCSA Lab Using Vagrant</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/rhcsavagrantlabsetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/rhcsavagrantlabsetup/</guid>
      <description>We are going to use Vagrant to set up two RHEL 8 servers with some custom configuration options. I will include some helpful Vagrant commands at the end if you get stuck.
In this guide, I will be using Fedora 38 as my main operating system. I use Fedora because it is similar in features to Red Hat Linux Distributions. This will give me even more practice for the RHCSA exam as I use it in day-to-day operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RHCSA Notes</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/rhcsanotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/rhcsanotes/</guid>
      <description> RHCSA Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8 (UPDATED) - Asghar Ghori
Here are my notes from Asghar Gori&amp;rsquo;s RHCSA book. Buy the book or read the reviews here.
Chapter 1: Installation Chapter 2: Interaction Chapter 3: File Management Chapter 4: Advanced File Management Chapter 5: Basic User Management Chapter 6: Advanced User Management Chapter 7: The Bash Shell Chapter 8: Process and Task Scheduling Chapter 9: Basic Package Management Chapter 16: Networking Chapter 17: Network File System </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Learn After CCNA</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/things_to_learn_after_ccna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tech/things_to_learn_after_ccna/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get overwhelmed with options after completing your CCNA. What do you learn next? If you are trying to get a job as a Network Engineer, you will want to check this out.
I went through dozens of job listings that mentioned CCNA. Then, tallied up the main devices/vendors, certifications, and technologies mentioned. And left out anything that wasn&amp;rsquo;t mentioned more than twice.
Core CCNA technologies such as LAN, WAN, OSPF, Spanning Tree, VLANs, etc.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>