<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools - Perfect Dark Mode</title>
    <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/</link>
    <description>Containers Calibre Web with docker distrobox vagrantguide Website Apache buildawebsite githubpageshugo hugorelearn SCSSandSASSinhugo Obsidian Free Obsidian sync Building a Dashboard How to use Templates How to use the dataview plugin YAML In Obsidian image_to_text Tracker Plugin Setup Git gitguide Vim vimguide Vim mode in bash Misc Calibre_Server emailserver iphonemigrate nextcloud pandoc Process-bookfusion-highlights proxmox_setup rsync Serial-in-on-linux Silverblue tmuxbook VS_Codium LEGO_BRICK_LABELS-CONTACT_SHEET Upcoming Projects: Searx Create my own searx search engine&#xA;go to https://searx.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:44:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Process Bookfusion Highlights in Vim</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/process-bookfusion-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:44:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/process-bookfusion-highlights/</guid>
      <description>Here are my highlights pulled up in Vim:&#xA;As you can see, Bookfusion gives you a lok of extra information when you export highlights. First, let’s get rid of the lines that begin with ##&#xA;Enter command mode in Vim by pressing esc. Then type :g/^##/d and press enter.&#xA;Much better.&#xA;Now let’s get rid of the color references: :g/^Color/d`&#xA;To get rid of the timestamps, we must find a different commonality between the lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nextcloud Guide</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/nextcloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:44:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/nextcloud/</guid>
      <description>This is a step-by-step guide to setting up Nextcloud on a Debian server. You will need a server hosted by a VPS like Vultr. And a Domain hosted by a DNS provider such as Cloudflare&#xA;What is Nextcloud? Nextcloud is so many things. It offers so many features and options, it deserves a bulleted list:&#xA;Free and open source Cloud storage and syncing Email client Custom browser dashboard with widgets Office suite RSS newsfeed Project organization (deck) Notebook Calender Task manager Connect to decentralized social media (like Mastodon) Replacement for all of google’s services Create web forms or surveys It is also free and open source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set up Hugo Relearn Theme</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/hugorelearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:45:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/hugorelearn/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Setup Adding a module as a theme Make sure Go is installed&#xA;go versionCreate a new site&#xA;hugo new site sitename cd sitenameInitialize your site as a module&#xA;hugo mod init sitenameConfirm&#xA;cat go.modAdd the module as a dependency using it’s git link&#xA;hugo mod get github.com/McShelby/hugo-theme-relearnConfirm&#xA;cat go.modadd the theme to config.toml&#xA;# add this line to config.toml and save theme = [&#34;github.com/McShelby/hugo-theme-relearn&#34;]Confirm by viewing site&#xA;hugo serve # visit browser at http://localhost:1313/ to view siteAdding a new “chapter” page</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Minimalist Website with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/buildawebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/buildawebsite/</guid>
      <description>Word Press is great, but it is probably a lot more bloated then you need for a personal website. Enter Hugo, it has less server capacity and storage needs than Word Press. Hugo is a static site generator than takes markdown files and converts them to html.&#xA;Hosting your own website is also a lot cheaper than having a provider like Bluehost do it for you. Instead of $15 per month, I am currently paying $10 per year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibre Web With Docker</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/calibre-web-with-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/calibre-web-with-docker/</guid>
      <description>I couldn’t find a guide on how to set up Calibre web step-by-step as a Docker container. Especially not one that used Nginx as a reverse proxy.&#xA;The good news is that it is really fast and simple. You’ll need a few tools to get this done:&#xA;A server with a public IP address A DNS Provider (I use CloudFlare) Docker Nginx A Calibre Library Certbot Rsync First, sync your local Calibre library to a folder on your server:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>