<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on Perfect Dark Mode</title>
    <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on Perfect Dark Mode</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Distrobox Guide</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/distrobox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/distrobox/</guid>
      <description>Github: https://github.com/89luca89/distrobox
Run native containers that have access to the host file system Creates an app launcher icon for the container
Launch gui apps from other distros natively. Even without spinning up the container first
Make separate shortcuts for separate distros in the terminal
Make a profile in the terminal for the container:
`distrobox-enter &amp;ndash;name ubuntu-20
Make sure to check the box &amp;ldquo;run a custom command instead of my shell&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nextcloud Guide</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/nextcloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:44:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/nextcloud/</guid>
      <description>This is a step-by-step guide to setting up Nextcloud on a Debian server. You will need a server hosted by a VPS like Vultr. And a Domain hosted by a DNS provider such as Cloudflare
What is Nextcloud? Nextcloud is so many things. It offers so many features and options, it deserves a bulleted list:
Free and open source Cloud storage and syncing Email client Custom browser dashboard with widgets Office suite RSS newsfeed Project organization (deck) Notebook Calender Task manager Connect to decentralized social media (like Mastodon) Replacement for all of google&amp;rsquo;s services Create web forms or surveys It is also free and open source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rsync Guide</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/rsync/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 06:19:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/rsync/</guid>
      <description>Using Rsync to sync a folder between two hosts I was using github to sync my notebook with my website. But that introduces some extra steps that rsync can easily eliminate.
Install rsync apt install rsyncTo upload files from your local computer to your server rsync -rtvzP /path/to/file root@example.org:/path/on/the/serverTurn the above script into an alias We will be adding an alias so you do not have to type the entire command above every time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beginners Guide to Git</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/gitguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 06:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/gitguide/</guid>
      <description>Commands Version $ git &amp;ndash;version
Show version of git installed Config $ git config &amp;ndash;global user.name &amp;ldquo;username&amp;rdquo; $ git config &amp;ndash;global user.email &amp;ldquo;email@email.com&amp;rdquo;
Let&amp;rsquo;s git know who you are Inizialize $ git init
initialize git on the current working directory Status $ git status
check the status of your git repo from your current working directory &amp;ndash;short flag will show a more compact version Short status flags are:
?? - Untracked files A - Files added to stage M - Modified files D - Deleted files</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set up Hugo Relearn Theme</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/hugorelearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:45:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/hugorelearn/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Setup Adding a module as a theme Make sure Go is installed
go versionCreate a new site
hugo new site sitename cd sitenameInitialize your site as a module
hugo mod init sitenameConfirm
cat go.modAdd the module as a dependency using it&amp;rsquo;s git link
hugo mod get github.com/McShelby/hugo-theme-relearnConfirm
cat go.modadd the theme to config.toml
# add this line to config.toml and save theme = [&amp;#34;github.com/McShelby/hugo-theme-relearn&amp;#34;]Confirm by viewing site
hugo serve # visit browser at http://localhost:1313/ to view siteAdding a new &amp;ldquo;chapter&amp;rdquo; page</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Minimalist Website with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/buildawebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/tools/buildawebsite/</guid>
      <description>Word Press is great, but it is probably a lot more bloated then you need for a personal website. Enter Hugo, it has less server capacity and storage needs than Word Press. Hugo is a static site generator than takes markdown files and converts them to html.
Hosting your own website is also a lot cheaper than having a provider like Bluehost do it for you. Instead of $15 per month, I am currently paying $10 per year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>