<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing - Perfect Dark Mode</title>
    <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/</link>
    <description>Writing is the single most important skill you can have in business and in life. We do it every day. Everyone is a writer. You write when you are sending emails. You Write when you are commenting code. You write when you make a grocery list.&#xA;AI is taking over and writing tons of low quality crap on the interwebs. Now is the best time to up your writing game and stand out over the robots.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>19 Biggest Lessons From Reading 100 Books</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/19-biggest-lessons-from-reading-100-books./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/19-biggest-lessons-from-reading-100-books./</guid>
      <description>I started reading non-fiction after hitting my rock bottom. I found people to look up to and saw that they were reading and learning constantly to better themselves. This inspired me to develop a reading and self improvement habit that I have continued for more than 10 years.&#xA;No single book has the ability to change your life. But the things you do, good or bad, over time, compound to extraordinary changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Journey With Addiction (NSFW)</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/my-journey-with-addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/my-journey-with-addiction/</guid>
      <description>In 2010, I was facing felony charges for distribution of drugs. I was a drug addict. Hook line and sinker. But never admitted that to myself. My drug of choice? Anything I could get my hands on. Cocaine, ecstasy, weed, Xanax, Oxycontin, ciggys, alcohol, ativan, seroquil, spice, mushrooms.. You name it.&#xA;Desperately wanting to avoid prison time, I did whatever I could to turn my life around. The potential pain in carrying on was too great to tolerate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing Off the Cuff</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/writing-off-the-cuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/writing/writing-off-the-cuff/</guid>
      <description>My favorite and by far easiest method of writing is writing off the cuff. You get your thoughts down and spring new thoughts to life. You are finding out what you know without referencing materials.&#xA;You are creating out of nothing. It is pure writing and creativity folded into one. We all have a “Muse” that will give to us whenever we ask.&#xA;All you have to do is start writing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>