<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Notes - Perfect Dark Mode</title>
    <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/</link>
    <description>The Blog Startup - By Meera Kothand Date Read: 2024-04-14. How Strongly I Recommend It: 8/10&#xA;If you are wanting to blog as a business, you need a sound strategy and business model. Filled with practical tips on identifying your audience, email strategy, branding, marketing, things to watch out for, etc. Definitely read this if you are wanting to start a blog.&#xA;Read my notes, or go to the Amazon page for details and reviews.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>123 Magic Notes</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/123magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/123magic/</guid>
      <description>The 3 jobs for you as a parent Control obnoxious Behavior (STOP behaviors) Encourage good behavior (START behaviors) Strengthening your relationship with your children Controlling obnoxious behavior (STOP Behaviors) This is where counting and break times come in. You will use counting and break times for STOP behaviors.&#xA;Taking Breaks and Counting A break is when parents and child can separate briefly so they can calm down and regroup. You do not talk about the behavior after the break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Master Reading List</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/master_reading_list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/master_reading_list/</guid>
      <description>In Progress I am reading way too many books at once. Goal is to cut this list down and read only 1 book at a time.&#xA;RHCSA Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8 (UPDATED): Training and Exam Preparation Guide (EX200), Second Edition Unconditional Parenting: Moving from Rewards and Punishments to Love and Reason The Other End of the Leash: Why We Do What We Do Around Dogs UNIX and Linux System Administration Handbook The Oxygen Advantage: The Simple, Scientifically Proven Breathing Techniques for a Healthier, Slimmer, Faster, and Fitter You 101 Labs - Linux LPIC1: Includes Linux Essentials The Linux Command Line, 2nd Edition: A Complete Introduction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Positive Dog Training Notes</title>
      <link>http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/thepowerofpositivedogtraining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://perfectdarkmode.com/booknotes/thepowerofpositivedogtraining/</guid>
      <description>Principles All living things repeat behaviors that are rewarding and avoid behaviors that are not You don’t need to punish dog to make behavior not rewarding&#xA;Instead, figure out how to make the right behavior rewarding enough&#xA;Reward behaviors you want&#xA;Ignore or prevent behaviors that you don’t want&#xA;Your dog already knows everything you are going to teach him Teach him the english words for those behaviors and make them very rewarding and fun Dogs can only learn one behavior for any particular cue</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>